Friends, you must have seen the quarter two results
of many companies so far. There is a
slight decrease in demand as compared to the regular
demand, but you
people were prepared for that too. Right, this was the August week,
September week, so it was not like that,
and the demand suddenly decreased, due to which we were
also asking to keep cash for a long time.
Because the economic data that used to come, the
data of October has
come optimistic, which
is an indicator of the sector being strong. Be it GST data,
auto data, even your PMAY
data, travel data, look, Wonderla
's results were not good, but the travel
data of October is still good, so this
shows that the sector was. Let's start your growth rate,
friends, first of all, open for you with the data of ICICI Lombard
General Insurance Company. Look,
what have I opened on here,
see the basic data is ICC Lombard
PSC India, from there I have given the investor
presentation so that I can know
which data the company is giving when it presents.  Important data: Companies
always share KPIs in their presentations,
which are performance indicators.
They talk about them for any company
because investors will also
know after some time. If the results
come, what should I look at first, what should I
focus on? So, like where they have mentioned
in the investor presentation right now,
before that, let me also tell you the
fair valuation of ICC Lombard General Insurance. So,
we will see how
their performance was, how is their
performance in the near term,
how is their performance now, and what can we expect from the long term? So, till now, what we have so far is in
front of you, friends.
When I shared the fair value of this Lombard General Insurance with you in general insurance,
I have also given you the data for general insurance. So,
you can also look at this data to
know where I should invest.
How many companies are there in overall general insurance,
like in this, the entire general insurance can be
divided into traffic and non-
traffic companies. Friends, here there are government companies and
here there are companies,
how much growth is the private company achieving?
How much growth is the government company seeing? Why are we
investing in private companies and
not in government companies? The growth is
strongest in private companies, secondly their margins are good,
their consistency is better.
I have given the data of different companies,
I will not tell you the details right now,
you should look at it carefully, we have discussed this many times
also, but you should know that in
private companies, ICC Lombard is the top company, these
people are doing the most, these people have the highest
market share, so which companies do you need to pay
attention to, right, you should look at that, there are
some different companies which are specifically
in healthcare, like Star Health,
friends, more claims come in healthcare, they come continuously, right, if it is
specifically in healthcare, the
growth here should be good because
we are under penetrated in healthcare, but there is
also that much risk, so ICC is
not specifically in healthcare,
so the risk gets divided equally or not,
like just now a new IPO has also come, Niva,
that too in healthcare,
so it increases your risk.  I would
invest in a diversified company like Bajaj is ADC, let's say their I am
not Pat DC Bank, similarly
Bajaj is a general insurance company, you can have a
large
share of Bajaj,
when these people's I came, friends,
in 2018, the data that was in front of us at that time, like
I tell you one ever some company, come with,
look at their data whether they are growing or
not, whether they are a leader or not, then
here we found that ICC was a
leading
company, grown in the past well, these
people have grown well, have made good
profits, I cannot say that it is a consistent profit, in and they have made losses,
friends, there are many companies in general insurance
which are making losses for years,
hardly one or two years they make profits,
most of the years they make losses, it is not like that,
in general insurance, ICC is the most consistent
profit making company, it means it is the most
consistent, we cannot say
that they have made profits all year,
sometimes there may be a
catastrophic event, like  Just
last year, there was a flood in Gujarat and there was a
flood situation in different places, so at such
times more claims come, like when Covid came,
a big event happened, at such times a lot of claims
come, but there is a risk
in insurance companies, so you would
not expect that you will get 100%
profit on your life, here sometimes
you have to face loss
and it is a big loss, you can face it in the future too, so
you have to select the company very carefully,
friends, you should not make the mistake of choosing a company whose half life is not in loss, otherwise it can
surprise you a lot, when
we started here, we prepared for growth, there can be a strong
profit on this, plus or
minus, now what did we
show on this, the
premium was of 100 crores, what is the
main thing, what is the main revenue of these people in general insurance,
friends, the premium generated
reached 28000-26000 crores last year, so there has been growth for these people,
I had expected that there would be a loss sometime.  It is
possible but look, even during Covid, these people came out with
profits, so this is big, that is, the
strength is increasing, the margin of the company
which was earlier two to three times,
expanded and
reached a margin of 5 to 10%, so now our safety is increasing, due to which
we came out with profits even during Covid, these
profits increased, due to which our
individual earnings increased, the reserve product
margin of the company remained stable, the prices of the company increased, we
cannot say that there has been a multi-year rally,
but as of now, whatever they had
given at 600-700, we
can say that now it is almost three to one times the rate, so an
average return, not an out performing
return, at a time when most of the general
insurance companies have made losses, if you get some
returns then keeping the past
in mind and keeping the future
in mind, the weightage should be given, you say that I will keep 10
weightage, it will not work, right, what will
we expect in the future, friends, we can expect that as the
penetration of insurance is less, it is more  There should be money too,
but now as India is earning more,
friends, in the coming times, we will see growth, see
how much I have expected, I am conservative.
Now friends, when we look at other countries which were
like us, which had low income, today the
insurance companies have grown there,
like look at China, today the insurance company is
in their top 10 companies, because
everyone wants safety, not money,
even if there is no safety, so my
hope for corvette growth is double, so
I am getting what I want, I
hope if this profit can happen sometime, we can
launch it once or twice in the coming years,
so I am prepared for it so that we can remain fit,
friends, my hope is that by 2030, today
's premiums will
cross 5,000 crores. By 2035, we will
see premiums of around one lakh crore, so it
can give us multi-year rally profit, which
today is around 2000 crores, the
profit will reach around 7500 crores and my earning is
Friends, you can take me further. On this basis,
friends, I expect my value of the stock to be
forward for value for
205. So, yes, I will get it. I can expect
multiple along with consistent profitability. It can be spent some
time in 10 years or sometimes prepare for a
year or two. Right now, this is the
long term scenario. What is going on right now? What
is the scenario? Right now, friends,
in the recent scenario, let me first tell you its chart.
This is your ICC
Loba. This is the quarterly chart. You can see it.
So, the IPO came. Yes, we were in this company. We got a
good response initially. Then friends, the Covid
era
came. The claims increased first and surprised us. Then
friends, this company is a big investor
because they have to maintain their solvency. So, they are
big investors. There was
negativity in the debt market due to which
their profits broke down again and its effect will be a
correction. Friends, we had said this at the time also.
Yes, you will see good improvement in profits in future. The
claims will reduce and  You
can see that in the last few months,
we can say that last year it rallied, so this general insurance and
life insurance are
underperforming and those which used to outperform earlier, may be
underperforming now, so
this cycle will also continue, you should
not be negative or positive about this, we have to adjust our
stance, as soon as you
see plus or minus in the results, so yes, you got a good
rally, last year in general insurance
got a breakout,
you can also see the reason why it did not work here, profit of 2000 crores
and there was no growth, the prices
were closed, now you will not get any profit in the growth of these paise,
you can get it, they are
already 30-40, this does not match the
growth of paise of 10 and also, as soon as the
stock correction comes, we
will see lifetime profit sale, I have given breakout,
looking at the recent trend, you can see the current trend,
friends, last year we saw growth in premium at 18, but
growth in premium was good,
growth was bound to come,
after Covid, people were scared anyway, whether or
not there was a rise  So we
need premium growth, anyway we had hope for
premium growth in 15, even then when the year ended, the
profit growth was not that good but the
improvement phase, if you look beyond the non-month, there was no
profit at all, there was
improvement in profit and this gave
hope that now we should see
both premium growth and profit growth in the coming time, the
results of Sector One, wonderful
sales growth, as far as premium is concerned, the premium
also grew well due to which you saw this breakout, now what about
your friends, here I have given the details of
Sector
One 20, premium growth friends, Sector Two premium
growth has become a bit muted, only the
growth of Sector One 20 is
good in front of the industry growth, low
growth is near to single digit, 11% growth, there has been a
slight decrease in premium growth, it is not good, it is
not what we expected, so first of all
you can see that the lack of premium growth has brought your stock
into correction on monthly basis, the
results came and the stock came into correction
Right,
instead of being an alert, the slight decrease seen in the premium,
friends, their investment income has
increased by 14% in quarter two, again good, so
why do they have investment income,
every insurance company has two
incomes, premium income is also good, their
investment income is also strong, so their
investment income will
come regularly because they have invested a big amount,
15% in equity, 85% as much as
they have invested in the debt market,
so the total income is 85%, you have seen the
expenses, but due to the increase in the stock market, the cost is
big this time, which is
right in quarter one, so what is the second alert, friends, the
expenses are bigger,
who increased them, I will see here in the cost,
their major cost
is claim, so one thing is becoming clear, the
claims came a lot in the quarter, 58%, but their
cost is of clean and the
claims increased from 27% in the same period of 15% premium, that is a
negative thing, but you guys remember
friends, catastrophic events like floods
In the states, in those states which are
contributors to GDP,
look at the premium
in India, but not all of India is able to buy insurance,
those states have more
security insurance where there is money,
so you should look at Gujarat, Tamil Nadu,
Telangana, that is, those states where yes
premiums are sold, there was a flood
situation there which caused losses, so be
prepared for such things, friends, this was bound to happen
and see, our claims have increased, there are
still claims outstanding, some things
may also be clear in the coming time, so the
main thing was the major cost, friends,
who gave the business, let's also pay attention to that, there has been
growth at 10%, but here also keep one more thing in
mind, friends, the premiums that have been increased, these people's
friends, around 6% of the premiums
come from health and there the growth is still good, the
growth of the economy is at 20%, the second
contributor is theirs, right,
friends, the growth in motor has decreased,
motor has affected friends,
I will tell you in their presentation also right now
with the exact data, the last
three months have not been optimistic for auto.
Why did the premium and profit come down? Because it was
investment income that affected them. But we have to keep the
internal things in mind.
Your expenses increased and the profits
decreased a little compared to what they were in Sector 1. Although there was a
little increase, this is a good thing.
Investment
income also plays an important role in increasing the rate. So, based on these data,
what should I expect? Tell me
what should I expect for this year.
Right, before I tell you my expectations, let
us also take some support from the company to know what the
company has to say. So, I
came here to the investor presentation and as
I scrolled down, look, the first
thing they have written is Gross Direct
Premium Income (GDPi). Friends,
in an insurance company, we will definitely see
how big the premium income is. Right, the
premium A1 which we just saw is bigger than 15-16,
these people are
bigger than 15-16. One thing is clear to us that
we are growing faster than the industry,
so it is a matter of happiness. Second, excluding
crops, if I do not look at crops, then
these people  We do not focus much on crops
because crop and mass health is such a thing
where the claims are the
highest, so smart companies will focus less
there, so they will
not focus on the GDP of 15, the industry which is bigger than 11,
we have seen this GDP,
we had seen that earlier also, this is the special thing to see,
see the combined ratio, when I gave you the value,
I have already written the combined ratio for you,
why is it important, what is combined ratio,
friends, we see whether the company is
in profit or not, we are
happy that the company is in profit, but it is
not necessary that it is real profit,
what will be called real profit, the company has paid premium,
premium, some expenses have happened and
suppose claims are made, then the company is in loss, so
why is it in profit because the company
has invested, due to investment income, or the company is in
loss, friends, this can be known from the
combined ratio, friends, it is above 100
anyway, that means more claims, still
103 was good, 102 was good,
last sector 100  The ratio has come, so
we always have to pay attention to the combined ratio,
see, in the last quarter, the
ratio was 103.8, so there is a slight
improvement from here, but when you
look at it quarterly, you will notice,
because that is very near term, the
ratio to last
is 90, so the combined ratio is a big
improvement, this is something worth noting,
friends, now we have to see whether this will continue, will the
combined ratio deteriorate in this also,
104.5 sorry, this is
not a good thing,
now should the combined ratio deteriorate further, what have
I written about it,
so we can know when we
look at their data, I am scaling it down a bit,
others have also given figures,
what is the return, average equity,
how much did they maintain, so this is a regular
thing, this is always, we have discussed all this,
we have also seen the combined ratio, which should be
checked regularly, let me
scroll it down and let  I
always check some important information. Growth is here.
Our complete chart of combined ratio is here.
Everything's book
value has
reached 6663.
To find the book value of an insurance company, you also need to look at their assets.
How much money have they invested?
You might have some difficulty in calculating it. So,
you can take guidance of their value.
I will find out. Look, I have
also written in the book value that your book
value was 267. Right, so yes, the book value
is bigger than last year and this has
helped me in running my stock. The
earnings are big. I have to see
how much business is coming from where. So, in HV,
like this, this whole motor is giving 17 plus how much
turnover. There is a big stake.
Right, recently, third party and D. These two are
seen separately because
their earnings are at 30. Friends, those who have good
health alone, they get good growth
but their risk is higher.
Why, we will also see this, but here this  Can C
is the entire distributor, now the crop which
gives the maximum claims there, but
marine gives big claims, but 4, right, that's great, you can see
how many claims are coming from where,
like loss ratio, loss ratio
should tell how many claims they get, so
what is their loss ratio in motor right now,
6490, total
motor A5 and what is it compared to 2024, in
which private car is at 52 and two wheeler is at
25.3, right, so these people traded in motor,
commercial car is at 22,
and in health, look at the loss ratio here,
what was the loss ratio, 65, in motor, now when I am
coming to health, a big figure is visible,
83.2, this is the loss ratio, so whatever
premium I brought in total and I am making a claim, then my
loss ratio is big, so I should understand
that if there is a health
company, it must have incurred more loss,
right, then it is good, ICC Lombard is
well balanced year and that is why friends, ICC
Lombard has the biggest profit  Like
in health also, the profit has increased than them, so Bajaj's
market share has increased more than them, but
why did ICC Loba's profit increase because it
is a well distributor, the rest of the company has a
comprehensive product portfolio,
everything has come up, Rat Property Quality 68,
average crop, you can see friends, loss ratio at 97,
so this is a risky game where one
should stay away, right, I am
not going into all the other things, study at your time peacefully, but
look at the combined ratio,
it used to increase,
earlier it was a matter of happiness, it has decreased, and it is
looking very good for us, wow, it has
decreased compared to the previous quarter, but
when you look at the quarterly data, you know that
their profit has decreased, but in quarter two it has increased
and that too was quite good in quarter one,
due to which it is looking good to you,
but internally see whether quarter two is high in near
two or not, friends, Rat Sal Things, considering all these
things, the investment
performance is getting good
because the market is also good, day market also
Okay, time, let me get into this topic.
Finally, the industry
penetration in India is low. You can see just
1% but
overall compared to other countries. So, all these data
tell you that the growth should be good in the times to come.
One more thing I would like to
share comes after thank you every
time. So don't end your presentation with thank you.
After that, friends, you will
get interesting data of loss ratio where the
loss of each segment is given.
Understand which business is bad and
which is bad. So, you can see which is
risky or not. Continue that risk.
And the second important data is this
catastrophic event historical.
Sometimes it seems that if many catastrophic
events come, what will happen to you? Friends,
they have given historical catastrophic events.
Whenever there was a flood in Jammu and Kashmir in 2014, how much was the
overall economic loss?
How much was the insured loss in that?
Look, it also depends on the state. Sometimes
you would have suffered a huge loss in the state.  Yes, but
we also have to see how much is the insured loss, what is
our company's share in that insurance loss? So, if
any big
catastrophic event comes, the insured loss
reduces and some percentage of it
falls on your individual company, like right now there
is Gujarat flood, so Andhra flood,
North India flood, Gujarat flood, etc. in
2024 the biggest loss friends, the insured
loss is
22 billion, see it is written, that means we
can say that
2200 is a big loss, friends,
you will not see such a big loss every time, so a
big loss of 2200 crores and that too
is a loss, so your company has suffered, the
rest of the loss has also gone to other companies,
but you suffered so much loss, right, that
also went out, okay, this time the company made a
profit, so that's great, so any such
big catastrophe comes, profits fall, right, one has to be
prepared in advance,
in which state it has come because if that state is
insured, then it will give more loss.  So
this is your important point,
what am I expecting, based on this data,
I am expecting friends,
I should get a growth of 13%, did I take it right or wrong,
tell me, look, it is 11%, but that was a weakness in auto, that's why it is
right, now auto became optimistic again from October, there was a lot of
growth in quarter one, so
I took a slightly better stance that is, let's say a
growth of 13%, so I
would expect margin friends, the
bearing rate is 9.2%, but I have been a little
conservative, the margin should not deteriorate, I should not lose a penny,
I have taken a little less % margin, according to
these, friends, what can I get, I expected a
sale of 1%, so a
premium of 29 crores this year, I am expecting a
lifetime high
premium, a margin of %, which would
take me to a profit of 6.61 crores, so I am expecting a good growth of 39%
this year,
so the growth is good, so friends, the
end friends, it should be good, so even though it is
in correction right now, do
n't worry too much because this was an event based correction
Due to some catastrophic event, there may be
some total in auto but it is right
friends, we can add in the fall, there should be
a good buying level friends, this is
anyway a break out level, so even before this
you will see buying on this.  So you should start with
SE I will keep a target of 361 for two years
yes what I expect from ICC
LoM I have expressed hope on this you must have
known last year when the year closed it was
39, the P was 43
still my P is 42 in this my P has become cheaper
because the earnings are big 45
earnings so the earnings have not
gone up that much on the contrary it has gone down a little bit so this is
in my favor friends I am not very worried
now further what I expected
profit growth is 39 friends I
reached EPS of 54 means it did not become very expensive so
anyway I will take P at 30
intrinsic P is 30 so P of 5 is more
so take that and take that to T so my
Peg ratio is favorable friends so this L
about ICC LoM investor
presentation was also told to you so that
you get guidance you people many times from outside
questions  The answer is awesome, tell me this,
tell me that, you get it with every company, so
what is the point of going to other's website and searching here and there,
so I will let me check this later and some query,
yes Vinay Kumar ji, good
morning Yogesh Chaudhary ji, yes good morning
Yogesh Bhai, you wrote sir,
sales growth, profit growth in double
digits from the page industry, canal government normalization and
ITD margin, what should we do, Vin Bhai, we have been
on negative page for the last two years, the last
or third quarter was when improvement was seen, there was
improvement in IIP as well and there was
improvement on Y as well, there was not as much lock element as we were
expecting, but the
results of Maniyarvar were absolutely mind
blowing, so we bought the results of Maniyarvar
again Vinay Bhai because we were
expecting that the results of the page would be explosive,
right, 48 lakh weddings in the coming time, so
you know that marriages are coming, 48
lakh, so Maniyarvar, if the page business is going to be
tremendous and already getting done
Sir, why did you take the result page, you know the
strategy, if your portfolio is 30 lakh
plus you can take it, or if it is less than 30 lakh then you have to go
to Manvar, right now the results of the page have
come, I liked them very much Vinay Bhai,
we did another ad on the same day of the page, so I am hoping
that now you will not see a decline in the page
and we are going to see its breakout, that
means now I can take the target of this and run the page,
I am expecting close to double digit growth in sales, right, so no, I don't want to worry, but I will do the
page on the next day,
Faizan Mansoori, yes sir, the GDP is showing at 7 to 8, then
why is it not reflecting in the company's results, look
Faizan, this is a growing industry,
general insurance, it is not like that, if the
GDP is at 7 to 8, then it should definitely
double, that is why we are doing it, so
over the decade Faizan, here we are going to
see 13-15 growth, so it will
remain in double digits only, right,
what else have you written, sir, Faizan, when will you release Q3 of IAL  I
think it should come in two-three days, I will have to
check on the BSE side, I do
n't remember, but it will come in two days,
its right, so I am expecting
General Insurance Clear, now let's take our
next result, friends, I am going for Nele's
result, let's follow this
same strategy, I will see what I told you, the
result comes quickly, see what you
say, what I was expecting,
see the presentation, so
now I am opening on Nele's result,
friends, it will be a little difficult for you,
they have changed their result
cycle, so no problem,
I have already written the past here,
friends, the sales were 2000 crores, when we
started investing, then it was 50 crores,
Ness Coffee is a brand, Maggi
is a brand, there are many different brands, Maggi has
given your Nele, so now you are with the brand, you can
expect good growth and now India is getting
ready for packaged food, that is,
double digit growth in packaged food in India.
Come rate because now in India, like before,
all these things
were not for rural at least but for urban, now Hindustan
can make product mix urban product
and premium product rate but now
their goods are being sold in rural as well, so these
people's focus is completely on rural as well,
we have seen turnover of 5000 crores
friends, last year it came to 19000 crores, so it has increased
four times now in crores, I am
saying last year i.e. financial year 2023
please try to understand
how much business happened in the year 2024, you do not know because
they have changed the cycle, now they have come in Indian cycle,
April to March friends, these people will
publish the results, then once they
change the cycle, will they stand for 15 months or
not, right, if they stand for 15 months
then you cannot say that wow, 24000 crores of 19,
this is 15,
so I am taking base year 2023 19000
crores turnover 3000 crores profit, my
share of EPS  That's why their price was
tremendous, 25 thousand.
They have never made any loss in their life since independence. They have been making losses
highly consistently. Whatever they earn, they distribute it
completely in dividends. Maybe
I have given this dividend distribution,
percentage, if
almost dividend is distributed then
such a company gets a high profit, you see, it keeps
increasing continuously, so such a company
remains multi-yearly in growth.
What do I expect from it, friends?
I will expect more than the past growth in the future because
this is a sector which is
in secular trend. Packaged food in India is going to have
explosive growth, so I will
not expect the growth of India at the time
when
what can we say to Indians, they could not buy
Maggi products, low income discussion, not spending,
but India is not past India, today
you are seeing friends, Indians are buying premium products, the
sales of all these are increasing, I am
expecting a conservative
growth of
12%.  You should get 15 this much. I am
taking a conservative stand of 12 on this. But
friends, I have never seen this company reach a turnover of crores.
Look at ICC Loba,
still I can expect this once or twice in 20 years.
So sometimes this is a brand, it will generate a
profit of 10,000. P.S. Friends, right now
theirs is yes, but we have 311
rights, but they have
divided the shares, so the EPS of 30 will
come now. So I will expect a multi-year rally along
with consistent profit.
Friends, I have taken the valuation at 000, but
such companies are far
away from the value. The more strength there is, the more
quality there is, friends, the valuation will increase over time. So
we need to prepare for this thing.
P.S. Theirs remains strong at 50,
so I have taken it at 50, so long
term is a good thing, but what is happening here right now, the
near term trend. I have
written the near term trend here.  So
till last year, like financial year 23, quarter
four of 24, I have taken it but I have
not taken financial 24, you know
why
it did not stick, you have the momentum in factor
four,
everything was good till last year but
momentum was seen in factor four, why was there the momentum, last
year the rains were not good
in rural areas, friends, you had the momentum and there
was a reflection in FMCT companies, a
single digit growth of 90% is not a good thing,
these are good, but we need both, we
need sales as well as profit, profit alone will not happen, there will be
sales, there will be profit, there will be profit,
sales will not work,
you can see the reflection of this in the chart, this is a
six month chart, first I will make it smaller, then
the
clarity, right, for how long you can see,
since the results were declared,
before that you saw the boom, the
results of 2023 were good, you saw the breakout in 2023
and we saw the lion running,
when this weakness came in quarter four, no problem, there is no need to do that
Sell ​​the goods immediately, otherwise run away from here, sometimes there is a
little
weightage like this, I am like this in quarter one also, friends,
when the results of quarter one came, how will you say growth at 6,
well, rate, then the rate and
profit, that is why their margins broke and the
share saw further correction, now the
result of quarter two, I wrote, these were in
front of 5, we came straight to 1.3, let's
open, tell me, I should be happy,
I should be prepared, you will be hit, if it
falls, pick it up, it will
not work until growth is not visible,
rate, we should look at ICC load, then
look here, at least there is business there, there is a
decrease in business here, the rain has fallen well, this is a good
thing, MSP will give them growth, whatever the
government has declared, it will be a big, we
can say, it will be a big bust,
in the coming time, for the rural areas, all those
crops which are called major crops, their
MSP will have a huge benefit effect till the end, the
second update of this month has just come,
crops  If you see the growth at 7 this time, the
crop growth at 7, the money will
go to the farmers, in rural areas
they have already received MSP, they will get good money
and growth as well, so I am hoping for gold,
this time I will not see 1.3, by the year end we will
see good growth, right, but the
current situation is the same,
we have seen a decrease in the sector as well, so
this is not good for the near term,
friends, what should I expect,
friends, you can see on the raw material major cost,
who is bringing it down, their
biggest share is of raw material, but it is
not big, it has decreased,
this is favorable, right,
material is not surprising,
inflation has not surprised them,
I have taken some more data here as well,
look at the segmental, milk products
gave good growth, they prepared dish
confectionery
powder, now I will come to friends,
what should I expect,
see my main person, this is
extremely conservative
expectation, extremely conservative.  But
I did not take the good thing into consideration,
I did not take the MSP into consideration,
I did not take into account the growth that has been expressed at 7, of course,
if I write, then what less will I
see than this, friend, in fact,
I will see the growth from the quarter itself, but let me prepare for bad, the
sales growth at 17.6, the margin rate, you
can see, the margin is flat,
in sector 2 it is 0.4, but overall friends,
their rate did not decrease, so there is no problem,
I will see the margin improving at
17.6, according to their data, a turn of 19000 crores, right,
profit of 6 crores, farewell, right, so what it comes in the
chart, the
indicator on it is coming, friends, it is not so good in October, do
not remain too negative, I will
advise everyone to do SIP, it can also happen,
friends,
improvement should be seen from the quarter itself, so also the prepared data
is bad, but it will not remain bad, if we
do this, then we will expect a target of 38,
three-one years,
right, those who  Here, those who bought on correction, those who
came to buy in the rally, they will definitely
face correction, so
friends, you should not be afraid of correction, if you take
in the rally, you will see the correction, you will see the
rally, so simple ST rate, I have
also given some of their data on this, see, they are
doing well in e-commerce also, nowadays e-commerce has
shown growth of 38% on this, Quick Commerce is also
doing well, you know Quick Commerce
Bank, if you wish, you can
order it, people order even small things on this, so
yes, Kit Kat Ness, Coffee, Maggi,
Milk Bud, etc., Commerce is also driving well,
all these
are absolutely beneficial things for them, rate out of home, robust growth,
potato
propelled, transforming, premiumization,
which I have talked to you friends, right,
read the different products calmly
so that you get an idea of ​​what these people are doing,
how are they moving forward, but this is about our
expectation,
friends, let me tell you the disclosure, yes, all these companies, we, our  They take it
in the fund but we take it, so
you are determined not to buy it, look at it as per your own understanding,
right, we are not a top provider at all, but
check the data and I told you the
whole method, where do you have to take someone's support,
go straight to here, see the investor presentation,
see the data, then
move ahead with confidence, then you are not dependent on anyone,
why do you need to ask anyone, why do you
need to look somewhere else, friends, right, so
we have shared the live results of many companies, yes, but the
time is such that
most of you may or may not be able to come on live,
it is right, but
you will get the video of this, there are recorded sessions, if
you have any query anywhere, you can tell me,
sorry, you can, and now friends, we will
come next week with other three companies, so
next week we will do two sessions like this, two sessions,
now next week we will
not be there on Saturday and Sunday because there is a program in Dubai, it is possible that we may get
a little busy, but still,
you guys keep doing it, right, friends, so it was
great discussing with everyone, or
see  Vinay Bhai has said that the result of L is today,
so
check that the result of Quarter 2 will be today itself, so
check it and tell us also how the result
came, right or so it was a great discussion with everyone, thank you so much
and best of luck to L,
Jai Hind friends. Thank you.